

# Ali Navidi

 Sari, Iran → +989339668289
 2 years of experience ali\_navidi24@yahoo.com
 Portfolio: alinavidi.dev/
 Blog: dev.to/westernal

Junior Front-End Developer

A 22 years-old frontend developer and a recently computer (software) engineering graduate, coding since 2018 and over 2 years of experience in developing websites, trying my best to write clean code, higher up the performance and improve the user experience, always seeking to improve my abilities and learn new things.

Skills: Tailwind Next.js React.js HTML ) CSS TypeScript Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB SEO Git Bootstrap Svelte JavaScript Remix

## Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.
- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Integrated enhancements into web design to improve user stickiness, smooth functionality, and boost load times.
- Translated UX and business requirements into elegant code solutions.
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customer.

Oben Origin co.

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

# **Projects**

## WESTERNAL | Frontend Developer - Backend Developer - Designer

Westernal is a social media based on songs, you can share posts that includes part of a song, the whole song or music videos with your followers and let the music talk for you!

 ${\sf JavaScript, CSS, Cypress, Next.js, MongoDB, Node.js, Express}$ 

## CINEMA | Frontend Developer - Designer

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Cinema is a platform for watching and downloading movies. A user can login and buy subscriptions to watch latest movies and series and learn more about cinema, actors/actresses and more. It's a website and PWA built with Next.js and TypeScript.

CSS, TypeScript, JavaScript, Next.js

### SARTEL | Frontend Developer - Designer

sari-sartel-westernal.vercel.app/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sartel is a website and PWA selling mobile phones and accessories.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

### DASHBOARD | Frontend Developer - Designer

An admin dashboard website and PWA built with Next.js and Chart.js to manage website data and content.

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

## Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Publications

### Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

**DEV Community** 

dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced